Hello everyone we are
I'm HINARIN KOUSEI!
Summer is almost over
It's finally the start of autumn.
That's right.
It's hot, but there's three inches of sunshine today.
But I can't open my eyes.
I really can't open my eyes.
What do you think of autumn?
Reading.
Halloween.
Field day
If you ask me...
What do you want to eat?
sweet potato, chestnut and pumpkin
It is indeed a sweet potato and chestnut pumpkin
Although there is a correct answer in it
I'd like to have a sweet potato digging showdown for this project!
I'm so happy!
I remember digging for sweet potatoes when I was little.
I remember doing it when I was a little girl.
In kindergarten, right?
It's been 14 years.
It's not that strong.
I looked it up... how to dig up a big sweet potato.
I heard there's no way.
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, we're all supposed to be mature enough to know better.
That's right.
I'm sure you can guess. You guessed it.
The criteria for this showdown are... simple.
Who has the heaviest potato.
Boom!
It's a showdown to see who can dig the heaviest potato.
We'll limit the number of shares each person can dig up to three.
That's right, three.
Aim for three.
Three for the showdown!
I really wanted to dig up all the signs in the field.
You're right.
That's amazing.
But... it's a competition, so it's all about who comes out on top.
Is there any kind of reward?
What would you like?
If there is.
What would you like to do?
Things.
I mean, for me, it's like...
I want to eat some kind of sweet food.
A sweet potato.
Sweet potatoes.
That's good.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Sweet potato.
Sweet potato
Oh, yeah.
That's cold.
For the treat, then. Julie told me. As for the treat, well, Julie told me about it.
A fall sweet called sweet potato sweet.
That's right.
It's okay, guys.
It's okay.
I'm glad.
We've decided to treat ourselves to a fall treat... the taro sweet.
Let's go for it.
Let's go for it!
We're going to start digging right away, but as you can see, we're going to get our clothes a little dirty, so we're going to change.
There's something I'd like to do.
What's that?
Just a few things. So I'd like to change clothes and move around, okay?
How do you fly?
Okay.
Let's go.
We're just gonna do it out of the blue?
We're going with "Se-o-no-Se-o-Me"?
Se-no
We're going on the Se-De-Se-De.
Ready?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Are you kidding me?
Okay.
Yay!
I got dressed.
My boots are a little uncomfortable.
Exquisite. Exquisite
Exquisite.
Cute.
She's cute, but she wears it so well.
She's wearing it well.
Julie, you're so stiff. I'm already stretching my arms with all the tightening.
I'm really serious about digging for potatoes.
You are?
Of course you are.
For sweets.
Let's go for it.
Let's dig right in.
Yes, sir.
Let's go for the sweet potato queen.
Yes, ma'am.
The sweet potato queen.
I'll do my best.
The sweet potato queen
The sweet potato queen.
The number of leaves seems to be important.
I'll take this one.
This one.
Is it big? I don't know.
It's pretty wiggly, my potato.
Is there any root at all?
Is this hard?
Is it hard?
Is it hard?Is it difficult?
I don't know.
It's pretty big, isn't it?
It might be pretty big.
It might be big.
It might be big!
I can't dig because I can't get to the roots at all.
Here we go.
Wait, it's not big.
The leaves are so big, I might have made a mistake.
It's so thin!
I'm scared.
It's the size of a champagne pencil.
No way!
I'm so hungry for sweet potatoes, I can smell them already!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, there's some kind of larva!
I'm scared!
Wait, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really no!
Put them back in the ground!
It's a real larva.
It's got a yellow head.
I wonder if it's sleeping.
It's moving.
I really don't want to do this.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I was sleeping. Did I wake you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, I'm sorry. Stop, stop, stop. Sorry.
I'm sorry for exposing you to the sun.
It's just that you've got some kind of a deep eye.
You can dig anything in here, it won't budge.
There you go.
It's moving a little bit.
Looks like bean sprouts.
Looks like purple bean sprouts.
Maybe it's the soil... or maybe it's the taste.
I don't know.
Find your target.
I don't remember it being this hard.
Julie's big.
This isn't great.
Wait a minute.
That's great.
It's a big one.
It's big.
It's kind of long.
It's long like a carrot.
Yay!
It doesn't come out at all.
A little thicker.
Here we go!
Go, go, go!
Maybe it's a little tiny.Maybe it's a little tiny.
Big, big, big, big, big, big.
Oh, I'm not fat anymore?
Maybe it's a little tiny.
She's here, too.
She's here too...
I can't write! I can't write!
Oh, I'm down!
Julie!
Julie failed the blue one!
No, the blue one.
Hey...
Hey.
On the head.
The head fell off.
Hey.
I tried to pull it out.
Oh, no...
Sorry, Blue.
Blue one!
Yay, Blue Mon!
Julie Mon is the blue one.
Julie Mon!
Oh, wait, Minnie came out, too.
No, that's not it. I'm the one who broke it.
I'm folding it.
I'm the one who broke it.
What am I supposed to do with this?
What should I do with this?What am I supposed to do with this?
It's a four-point sweet potato swing. I can almost smell the sweet potato.
What? Wait a minute!
Wow!
Oh, man!
That's amazing!
It's so good!
Oh, my God!
This is amazing!
I won, I won, I won!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
I won!
That's great... a supermarket graduate.
We should be thankful.
It's so hard to get one of each of these.
Yuka, I'm still not in love with you.
It's pretty deep.
A little
You're all early.
Ito style
Two cute twins.
Yay!
I'm getting a little attached to them.
Maybe I should give them names or something.
This one has a leaf on it.
Yoko, because it has a leaf on it.
This one has something white in it.
Shiroko.is it okay if I use albino?
albino character twist, twist, twist
Shiroko difficult, characteristic
Shiroko-suke
It's true, this one's tougher.
It's more robust.
For a boy
Shirosuke.
This is Yoko.
I want to watch over him.
Not at all.
I couldn't dig at all.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Here... here's the girl...
Oh, wait, did you get it?
It's gone again.
It's so hard to get the baby.
You're digging so fast.
I think we'll dig faster with Jiri.
I'm going to pull it.
I'll pull it out.
All right.
First one.
Wow.
Wow, absolutely.
I got it.
I'm so attached to it.
I feel like I've been digging for 15 minutes.
Yay!Yay!
I have a pretty big confidence in this one.
That's a great winning book.
Yay!
So, I dug it out.
Wow!
That's a near-angle!
Right in front of me is the one I got myself!
My own child!
It's a sweet potato that tastes like my own child.
Each of us took three shares.
The biggest of them all
The one that weighs the most wins.
But Rico's... but Rico's is too strong.
Riko's is a little stronger.
We won't know until we measure them.
So, let's start the search.
Okay, let's start with the first five.
Julie, let's start with you.
I've decided on this one.
Great.
What's her name?
Name?
Okay.
Imozou.
Imokura is nice.
I'll go with Imokura.
Let's go with Imokura.
I'll put "Imokura" on it.
Go for it! Hang in there.
Light
Hold on.
What?
440 grams?
Oh!
I don't know, Shishio.
I'll change my name to Shishio.
I'll change it to Shishio.
Okay, Shi-ShiOh.
I'm Shishio.
Four-foot-two.
440g
Blue size
Please
Oh, it's big
Oh, that's big.
460 grams.
White, white.
White.
Hotenishirou.
Hotenishi.
Good.
Hotenishi Shirou.
Relative to Onishi
It's okay.
They're kids and they're all different.
No, it's fine.No, I'm fine.
I shouldn't.
Okay, thank you very much.
Next
Mai-chan.
I'd like to go.
Yes, ma'am.
What's this?
Juwaki's face.
Juwaki's face
I'm sure.
Juhwaki's stuff
Juhwako
Jwako
It's a Jwakko.
Oh?
What?
That's amazing.
That's great.
Five hundred.
Five ninety.
Yay!
It was 590!
Strong.
Next.
Who's next?
Riko.
Thanks, Riko!
Here you go.
Riko.Riko
Hotchpotch is this.
It's strong.
Too strong.
Amazing, isn't it?
That's enough.
You can take it, can't you?
It's bigger than that.
It's great, isn't it?
What?
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
What?
Huh?
Yumika is amazing.
What?
Huh?
Eight forty.
Oh, my God.
Yashiro
Yay!
Eight hundred and forty.
It's bigger than Riko's face!
That's great.
That's great!That's great.
Yay Yashio!
That's great!
Last Yuka
Yes, I think there are more than 840 of these.
I think this is more than 840
I'm not...
I don't know yet.
Then aim for one kilo.
That's right.
I'm going for Ichiko.
Go for it!
Ichiko.
I'll go!
I'm going!
1 kilo
1 kilometer
One kilometer.
Let's see...
Grams
O
Early 70
repentance
face of a person
thank you
Thank you very much.
What?
Is there still a line?
That's great.
So, the winner is...
Riko!
That was amazing!
That was the prize, wasn't it? And the sweet potato treat.
That means you get to eat it, Riko!
That's great!
I'm jealous. Let's all eat together.
That's so sweet of you.
If I ate the sweet potato all by myself...
It would be a little sad if I ate the sweet potato all by myself.
So today, we had a sweet potato showdown!
Yay!
If you liked this video
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel, click the "Good" button, and leave a comment!
That's all for now!
That's all for now, this is Minariko-chan!
Bye bye!
ED
by H.